Finding aid to the Office of the President Thomas Corwin Mendenhall Files. CA.MS.00032
Smith College Archives
- SLIDES OF THE INAUGURATION IN THE A/V COLLECTION
  - Going through audience, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Delegates ascending platform (missing), OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Ada Notestein speaking, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - President, and Hazel Coe, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Someone speaking, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Symbols of office, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - President speaking, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Speaking: the president (missing), OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Martha Wilson tower, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Terrace, the Coes, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Terrace, Mrs. Neilson and an alumna, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - President's House, interior, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Reception, Mendenhalls, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)